Alex Istranin

QA ENGINEER

Details

Moscow Russian Federation +79193674386 istraninalex96@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

Skills

Manual Testing

Youtrack

Git

JIRA

C++

Python

SQL

Postman

Selenium

Bugzilla

Java

Hobbies

Learning languages, Hidden object Games, Trecking, Powerlifting

Languages

English

Italian

Profile

Quality assurance engineer by vocation with extensive knowledge of engineering principles, theories, specifications and standards. Leadership, responsibility and more than three years of experience. Proven track record of completing complex projects ahead of schedule. Substantial experience in analyzing problems and proposing processes that help alleviate them. Able to oversee the quality assurance process and work with other professionals to ensure the successful completion of projects.

Employment History

QA Engineer, unannaunced project, Moscow

NOVEMBER 2021 - JANUARY 2022

Manual functional and UX testing

Compilation of checklists

Creation of test cases

Finding bugs

Making bug reports

Technical support, PPG, Moscow

JULY 2018 - NOVEMBER 2021

Drafting and translation of technical documentation

Customer support

Testing software, web, mobile applications

The holding of trainings

Checking devices for quality

Organization of business processes

Software installation and support

Education

MBA, Ural Institute of Commerce and Law, Yekaterinburg

SEPTEMBER 2001 - JULY 2007

Courses

Programming and Databases Fundamentals, Bauman Moscow State Technical University

JANUARY 2021 - FEBRUARY 2021

Manual Testing, BE-Tester School

SEPTEMBER 2021 - OCTOBER 2021

Test Automation with Selenium and Python, BE-Tester School

OCTOBER 2021 - NOVEMBER 2021